Gourmet Glasses
I'm home!
I'm starving!
Mum, is our dinner ready?
I'll cook it in no time!
What all is in today's menu?
Sardine!
Sardine is very healthy for your body.
"All-You-Can-Eat!"
What happened?
Today's menu is Sardine!
Sardine?
I HATE Sardine!!!
But love-hate relationship with food isn't good.
But...!!!
An idea!
What are you gonna do?
Take a deep nap. Being awake makes me hungry...
What a hopeless boy!
Gourmet Glasses!
What glasses, again?
The Gourmet Glasses!
Wear this when you're eating and the cuisine will look like your favorite food.
But the taste will be the same as Sardine?
Even if the appearance changes...
Do you really think I'd pull out such a useless gadget?
That means?!
The taste will change too, of course!
I'm gonna try it out!
Nobita, Dora-chan, it's dinner-time!
Wash your hands properly!
Looks yum!
I'm gonna dig in!
How tasty!
What happened to him?!
More please!
Mum, it's your chance!
Good, Nobi-chan!
I'll give you more and more!
Here you go!
This Umetate looks so tasty!
umetate?
Nobita-kun, it's Yakitate, not Hagetate.
Yum!
This is the best!
I'm so full!
I don't need food for the time being.
What a handy gadget!
I know, right?
In 22nd century, the pilots visiting earth use this.
Since they'd be fed up with earth's cuisine in no time!
I see.
Now, let's see.
What are you doin'?
Seeing food and dessert!
What will you pull out?
Chips?
No, this is very tasty Dorayaki.
I see. So you perceive it as Dorayaki?
But what a weird Dorayaki.
Seeing you enjoying your meal makes me drool too.
I'm taking these.
You're so mean!
It's my turn, now.
What a delicious looking cookies!
I'm having these!
How tasty!
Hey, hurry up!
Let's begin eating!
It's fish once again today.
But I have the Gourmet Glasses with me!
Yay, I'm eating Hamburger Rice.
I'm full!
Yes!
You ate it fully without leaving any.
Yes, sir!
What's going on here?
Nobita-san, you're so cool, I hate this too.
It's a secret, but you see...
A secret?
It makes me see my favorite food?
I wonder if it's true?
Looks tasty!
I'm digging in!
Upsy-Daisy!
Nobita-san!
Nobita-san, thanks for the glasses.
How'd it went?
It was very tasty! It even changed the flavor. I was little surprised.
With these glasses you can eat any ill-tasting food with ease.
It makes the full course more exciting!
So Dora-chan lent you these glasses?
Yep. Wish he gave me these glasses forever.
That way I could eat my favorite food every day.
Of course, I'll lend these to you whenever you feel like having 'em!
Why, thank you!
So you were using these. We knew it was strange!
Give 'em back!
It's unfair of you to keep these for yourself!
These are just ordinary glasses.
Yup, so give me back!
Big bro!
Oh ,it's you, Giko.
What are you up to?
What's with those eyeglasses?
Oh, you were shopping?
Dinner ingredients?
What's for dinner today?
What a tasty-looking banana!
Banana?
Hey, Giant! What are you doing?
Are you blind or what? I'm peeling off banana.
But that's a carrot.
Are you nuts? This is banana!
Diggin' in!
Oh, bro!
You're like a horse
What an tasty looking apple!
Apple?
You'll fall sick if you ate it without running it down in water!
But what's the problem?
But that's an onion!
Why are you saying it's an onion? What's wrong with you guys?
Hey, Suneo, cut it out!
Why do you say it's an onion?
You're the one who should quit fooling around, bro!
What?
Why are you wearing these weird glasses?
So spicy!
Nobita!
How dare you fool my senses!
But I'm innocent!
Shaddup!
Stop, Nobita!
Quickly! Gimme the glasses!
Stop!
How unreasonable of him!
He's so stupid!
I know, right?
Nobita, Dora-chan, please lend me a hand here!
Oh, Nobita's glasses? What a weird design!
This is beer!
I'm so glad she's making tonkatsu!
Yup. I can enjoy it without those glasses.
Daddy...
Nobita, how considerate of your mum to give me this exquisite beer.
What now? Dad's drunk by drinking tea!
Let him enjoy once in a while!
Right!